vistahigherlearning.com 2016-05-07

# Privacy Policy | Vista Higher Learning

### PRIVACY POLICY APPLICABLE TO:

Vista Higher Learning Website ([www.vistahigherlearning.com](http://vistahigherlearning.com/home)) (the “VHL Site”)

This Privacy Policy describes certain information that Vista Higher Learning, Inc. (“Vista Higher Learning”) collects through the VHL Site and how we use that information. Please note that this Privacy Policy applies solely to our online information-gathering and dissemination practices in connection with the VHL Site, and does not apply to any of our practices conducted offline.

Vista Higher Learning reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to change, modify, add or remove this Privacy Policy in whole or in part, at any time. Changes will be effective when notice of such change is posted at [http://www.vistahigherlearning.com/content/privacypolicy/](http://vistahigherlearning.com/privacy-policy). Your continued use of the VHL Site or any other products or services offered by Vista Higher Learning after any changes are posted will be considered acceptance of those changes. By using the VHL Site and any other products or services offered by Vista Higher Learning, you agree that you have reviewed, understand and accept this Privacy Policy, and that Vista Higher Learning may collect and use your information as set forth below. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the VHL Site.

Unless otherwise agreed in writing by Vista Higher Learning, the data collected on the VHL Site belongs exclusively to Vista Higher Learning, and Vista Higher Learning is solely responsible for creating and maintaining this policy.

#### 1\. INFORMATION VISTA HIGHER LEARNING COLLECTS.

**Vista Higher Learning Store**

Vista Higher Learning is pleased to offer students through the VHL Site the opportunity to order their required course materials directly from our Vista Higher Learning Store (the “Store”) (www.vistahigherlearning.com/store/). If you make a purchase from the Store, Vista Higher Learning will share your credit card information and any other information required to process your transaction, such as name, email address, shipping address, billing address and school name with its third party payment processor, Authorize.net. Vista Higher Learning urges you to review Authorize.net’s privacy policy. (See [www.authorize.net/company/privacy](http://www.authorize.net/company/privacy/) ). Vista Higher Learning is not responsible for Authorize.net’s privacy and security practices.

Vista Higher Learning has engaged Hudson Software Corporation (“Hudson”) to provide technical support regarding use of the Store. Hudson may request information from or about you in order to provide technical support that you request. Any information provided to Hudson is subject to Hudson’s privacy and security practices and is not protected by this Privacy Policy. Vista Higher Learning urges you to contact Hudson regarding its practices prior to disclosing any information to Hudson, as Vista Higher Learning is not responsible for Hudson’s privacy and security practices.

Vista Higher Learning does not knowingly sell products or services to anyone under the age of 13 years via the Store. If you are under 13 years of age, you should use the Store only with the consent or involvement of a parent or guardian.

**General**

Certain identifying information is automatically collected when you visit the VHL Site, including the IP address from which the VHL Site is accessed. We may collect identifying information that allows us to track the number of visitors we receive and the way they navigate through the VHL Site. The types of identifying information collected include the date and time you accessed the VHL Site, the page or pages you visited and images you accessed, the website you arrived to the VHL Site from and the website that you depart to as well as the IP address of the computer being used to access the VHL Site. We may use IP addresses and anonymous demographic information in the aggregate to share with advertisers and market researchers, and to improve the design of the VHL Site to better serve our customers and otherwise for Vista Higher Learning business purposes. While it may be possible to correlate this information to particular individuals, we do not generally do so. We may share this aggregated information with other third parties. We reserve the right to analyze anonymous demographic information or otherwise correlate it to particular individuals in order to investigate potentially unlawful conduct and/or breaches of this Privacy Policy. For example, we may report to appropriate school and law enforcement authorities any IP addresses and correlated email address that is associated with multiple unsuccessful code redemption attempts.

#### 2\. WHAT VISTA HIGHER LEARNING DOES WITH THE INFORMATION IT COLLECTS.

**Use of Information**

Vista Higher Learning may use the information we collect for our business purposes, including to process your requests and transactions, personalize the types of information you receive from Vista Higher Learning, assess trends in your use of the VHL Site or purchases of products or services, develop content and functionality that helps us better serve your needs, and improve the service and products we provide.

Information and materials submitted by students in connection with courses offered through the VHL Site will be made available to school officials, including instructors, with legitimate education interests in such information and material. Such information and materials includes the student’s full name, VHL Site username, email address, student ID (if provided), the student’s substantive course work, any student recorded and submitted communications on the VHL Site, uploaded documents, site usage information (including time on site, time spent on each course-related activity, submission dates and times for course activities), score and grade information, login history, account creation date and time, and enrollment history.

We may also use the information we collect through the VHL Site to offer or furnish additional products and services, such as training opportunities and updates, and engage in advertising and marketing activities. You may opt-out of receiving these messages. The following options are available to opt-out of receiving these messages:

  * Send email to online@vistahigherlearning.com 
  * Send written correspondence to:

Vista Higher Learning  
500 Boylston Street  
Suite 620, Boston, MA 02116 

  * Call (800) 248-2813
  * Fax (617) 426-5215 
  * By using the “unsubscribe” link on any emailed correspondence from Vista Higher Learning

**User Name and Password Information**

If you lose or forget your login information, you may contact us and ask us to change your password to a temporary password. You authorize us to, upon request, send your login information to your email address of record. This means that if you give someone else access to your email, they might have access to your account. **Further, we may provide to secondary school instructors with a method of resetting a student’s password for students who have indicated to us that they are enrolled at the instructor’s school. This means that, if you are a secondary school student, it is possible for instructors at your school to view your VHL Central Site account.** We will not knowingly provide instructor login information to any student.

**Disclosures of Information to Third Parties**

We may share nonpublic personal information with affiliates and other third parties that assist us in providing our services or products or otherwise responding to your requests or orders. Vista Higher Learning may transfer any information in its databases, including but not limited to nonpublic personal information, to an affiliate or third party as part of a transfer of business assets.

Vista Higher Learning may also release nonpublic personal information in special cases in order to comply with requests from law enforcement and government agencies, to protect Vista Higher Learning’s rights and to protect customers and others and otherwise as permitted or required by law. We may do so when we believe in good faith that disclosing this information is otherwise necessary or advisable, including, for instance, to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interfering with the rights or property of Vista Higher Learning, another user, a school with whom any user is associated. or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. This includes reporting unsuccessful code redemption attempts and other related information to appropriate school and law enforcement authorities.

**Links to Other Sites**

Vista Higher Learning may provide links to other websites for your convenience. Vista Higher Learning does not endorse and is not responsible for any third party websites, products, services or business practices. Vista Higher Learning assumes no responsibility for the privacy or security of information you provide to any third party through linked websites or any other means. We urge you to review the privacy policy of any website that you visit.

#### 3\. SECURITY

**Username and Passcodes**

Instructors and students must keep their VHL Site user names and passwords private and may not share them with any third party, even on a temporary basis. Vista Higher Learning cannot be responsible for unauthorized access to accounts gained through use of user names and passwords obtained from the authorized user. If you suspect that your password has been compromised, please contact Vista Higher Leaning, immediately.

**General**

While Vista Higher Learning strives to protect nonpublic personal information and takes reasonable steps to ensure the security, integrity and confidentiality of such information disclosed to us, we cannot guarantee the security, integrity or confidentiality of any information you disclose and you do so at your own risk. Vista Higher Learning does, however, use 128-bit SSL encryption for transmission of sensitive information on the Store, which has been certified as a Thawte Trusted Site.

#### 4\. COOKIES & INTERNET BROWSER SETTINGS

We use cookies. “Cookies” are small pieces of data that can be stored by an Internet browser for visitor tracking purposes. Cookies cannot access your hard drive or send information about your computer system. Cookies are just simply a data storage system. We use them to study visitors’ use of the VHL Site and to improve our services for you. Most Web browsers accept cookies, but the “help” menu on your browser should give you options for preventing, accepting, or receiving notice of new cookies. You can configure your web-browser to disable cookies, but doing so will impair your use of the Store portions of the VHL Site. Vista Higher Learning requires that its customers configure Internet browsers to enable session cookies from the Store portions of the VHL Site in order to use the Store functionalities.

#### 5\. CHILDREN

The VHL Site is not intended for children under the age of 13, and Vista Higher Learning does not intentionally collect nonpublic personal information from children under 13. If you have reason to believe that we have collected nonpublic personal information from someone under 13 years of age, please let us know.

#### 6\. CONTACT VISTA HIGHER LEARNING

If you have any questions or concerns about Vista Higher Learning’s use of non-public personal information or about this privacy statement, please contact Vista Higher Learning at:

**Vista Higher Learning:**

500 Boylston Street 

Suite 620 Boston, MA 02116 USA 

**Phone:**

(617) 426-4910 

(800) 618-7375 

**Fax:**

(617) 426-5215 

**Email:**

online@vistahigherlearning.com

Vista Higher Learning takes concerns about privacy and use of personal data seriously, and will reply as quickly as reasonably possible to any report of concern.

Last Updated May 21, 2012
